So, I want to come back to Hyperwrite and I want to use it writing an article, right?
So, let's say that I want to, for example, write an article about how to get yourself a perfect resume or CV, right?
So, hey Hyperwrite, I want you to write me an article about how to get together the perfect CV resume possible and points to be taken care of,
and a checklist, finally, for a perfect resume, write it for me, right?
And I submit by command and I wait to see what the Hyperwrite does for us.
So, it says, "All right, let's dive into crafting an article."
And it says, "How to put together the perfect CV, a practical guide to landing your dream job, right?"
And it is writing it for me, right? It also created me this checklist over here.
And that's pretty much all that we have. It's very similar to the other chatbots that we have been using.
We also can upload a file using this icon over here, this button over here.
We don't need to for now, you know? That's what I assume.